[{"answer": "Well I'm doing the same things that we talked about in that interview.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How are you coping since I last spoke to you as a family?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I had a child that passed away and it's been 36 years and I've accepted it as much as I can and I'm living a normal life now but my struggle is trying to again, get peace with myself for why.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Bonnie what's your question for Rick Warren?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, well again as I said, it would be very easy for God to remove all the evil in the world, just take away my freedom to do it and your freedom to do it.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Rick I suppose the general question on the back of that is, how can a loving God put people through such terrible pain of taking a child away?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "A month before he took his life.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "When did he finally get this gun?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "He told me that he -- he told me everything and he told me that he had found somebody finally on the internet who would sell it to him and it had to be super encrypted and it had to be, you know, this whole process and he begged me to help him because he couldn't figure out the process and again there's so many moments of terrible choices with mental illness.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Who he got it from?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "I think one of the reasons why it's being hard to tackle is because there are so many guns out there.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "No one seems to be tackling this, what is the answer, how do we get to grips with this?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "I don't know how they're going to attack it politically.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "What does that tell you about the state of the debate about it, before anything else?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Well I think you hit it on the head Piers when you said that the internet has really made a megaphone.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "And how do we tackle it?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Oh of course.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "And you've actually -- you've had this?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "On Monday they closed down 13 just on Monday.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "600?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well absolutely, first he just have the authority of speaking as a man who spent his life helping the poor.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Now it probably is pure political as well as everything else but in the end, isn't it the Pope just effectively standing up as he always has done for the poor about what he said?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, I don't get to change what God says is right and what God says is wrong.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Are you recognizing that there is this seemingly unstoppable movement?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I -- certainly the Bible -- it says God created marriage.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Well, that term is from the Bible Right?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Most diet plans are pretty simplistic 'cause they only deal with food and fitness.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "How are you going to get me healthier in 40 days?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "This one is actually on physical health and -- and actually the reason why is that I discovered that a lot people want to change, make changes in their life but they don't have the energy to make changes.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "... so that's impressive doesn't it?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "You know what's extraordinary Piers is that people change together in community.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Why should spirituality, the power of prayer, any of that stuff have any effect of my ability to be fit or lose weight?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "So there are a 140 studies now, that say as your weight goes up, the actual physical size, and function of your brain goes down.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "How are you going to convince people in their heads, never mind anything else, to come and do this because if this is the master plan you got to persuade them?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "When the brain smaller as you get fatter?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "The person with the good bottle of Jack Daniels.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "The person with the good brain or the person with the bad brain?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "So start reading the labels so get on the internet--", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Does it matter?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I mean it's very simple.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "So tell me what are you hoping, well these audience said, many of them have tried and failed with diets through their lives what is the key take away here from this book that can change things?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "Yeah, plant food, nuts, seeds, beans, whole of grains--", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Plant food?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "Me chicken, fish, all of those things are foods.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Can you eat as much wings as you like?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "Sugar, flour, processed foods, factory foods,(inaudible), corn syrup, trans fats, MSG all these things that are -- the abundant things in our diet that are driving addiction--", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "What are the biggest no no's?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well there are three things.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What do you think has been the most effective thing for you in terms of loosing weight?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "You know, Christmas, there's three purposes of Christmas.", "docId": "131206pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "And Rick just a final question for you, obviously you said, the most difficult year of your life, how will you be spending Christmas this year as a family?", "qSentId": 403}]